// var windowTimeout = setTimeout(function() {
//     alert("Are you ready for trivia? Timer starts immediately...")
//   }, 1000);
var startScreen;
var scoreOverScreen;
var timeOutScreen;

var timer;
var timeCount = :60;

var correctAns = 0;
var wrongAns = 0;
var missed = 0;

var timeInterval;

function startTimer (
  timeInterval = setInterval(resetTimer, 1000);
)

  function start() {
    $("#countDown").html("5:00");
  }
  
start();
  var questions = [
  {  
  question: "1. Question1?",
  answers: [
    "answer1a",
    "answer2a"
    "answer3a"
    "answer4a"
  ],
  correctAnswer: "answer1a",
  name: "topic1"
  }

  {  
    question: "1. Question1?",
    answers: [
      "answer1a",
      "answer2a"
      "answer3a"
      "answer4a"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "answer1a",
    name: "topic1"
    }

    {  
      question: "1. Question1?",
      answers: [
        "answer1a",
        "answer2a"
        "answer3a"
        "answer4a"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "answer1a",
      name: "topic1"
      }

      {  
        question: "2. Question2?",
        answers: [
          "answer1b",
          "answer2b"
          "answer3b"
          "answer4b"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "answer1b",
        name: "topic2"
        }

        {  
          question: "3. Question3?",
          answers: [
            "answer1c",
            "answer2c"
            "answer3c"
            "answer4c"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "answer1c",
          name: "topic3"
          }

          {  
            question: "4. Question4?",
            answers: [
              "answer1d",
              "answer2d"
              "answer3d"
              "answer4d"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "answer1d",
            name: "topic4"
            }

            {  
              question: "5. Question5?",
              answers: [
                "answer1e",
                "answer2e"
                "answer3e"
                "answer4e"
              ],
              correctAnswer: "answer1e",
              name: "topic5"
              }

              {  
                question: "6. Question6?",
                answers: [
                  "answer1f",
                  "answer2f"
                  "answer3f"
                  "answer4f"
                ],
                correctAnswer: "answer1f",
                name: "topic6"
                }

                {  
                  question: "7. Question7?",
                  answers: [
                    "answer1g",
                    "answer2g"
                    "answer3g"
                    "answer4g"
                  ],
                  correctAnswer: "answer1g",
                  name: "topic7"
                  }
                
                  {  
                    question: "8. Question8?",
                    answers: [
                      "answer1h",
                      "answer2h"
                      "answer3h"
                      "answer4h"
                    ],
                    correctAnswer: "answer1h",
                    name: "topic8"
                    }
]
// make timer
  //set to decrease by seconds
    //reset after time out or game over

//make questions
  //make answers
    //set to store score if true or false

//make start screen
  //starts countdown and first question

//make final screen
  //shows score when game finished or time up

//make reset
  //